{"type":"multiple","question":"Which book contains the character 'Sebastian Flyte'?","correct_answer":"Brideshead Revisited","incorrect_answers":["Breakfast at Tiffany's", "The Age of Innocence", "An American Tragedy"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"If you're killing a goomba, what game are you playing?","correct_answer":"Super Mario Bros.","incorrect_answers":["Zelda", "Call of Duty", "Halo"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"What is the fancy name for women's underwear, which is derived from a French word?","correct_answer":"Lingerie","incorrect_answers":["Corsetry", "Foundation garments", "Intimates"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"What type of alcoholic beverage is bourbon?","correct_answer":"Whiskey","incorrect_answers":["Beer", "Wine", "Rum"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which band was Chester Bennington a member of?","correct_answer":"Linkin Park","incorrect_answers":["Alice in Chains", "Hollywood Undead", "System of a Down"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which word is defined as 'to engage in cut-and-thrust fighting with knives'?","correct_answer":"Snickersnee","incorrect_answers":["Curmudgeon", "Xertz", "Cattywampus"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which actor played the role of Robin Hood in The Adventures of Robin Hood?","correct_answer":"Errol Flynn","incorrect_answers":["Sidney Poitier", "Robert Mitchum", "Clint Eastwood"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"What was Marilyn Monroe's last film?","correct_answer":"The Misfits","incorrect_answers":["The Freaks", "The Outcasts", "The Pariahs"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which American grunge band released the studio album 'Black Gives Way to Blue'?","correct_answer":"Alice in Chains","incorrect_answers":["Poison", "Three 6 Mafia", "The Velvet Underground"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"'Mickey' was a one hit wonder in 1982 by which artist?","correct_answer":"Toni Basil","incorrect_answers":["Wild Cherry", "Edwyn Collins", "Terry Jacks"]}"comment":"""stats":"50"